[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What British singer recorded her biggest hit, Downtown in 1964?", "correct_answer": "Petula Clark", "incorrect_answers": ["Myleene Klass", "Amy Winehouse", "Lulu"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "When the first Apollo astronauts landed on the moon they left a memento behind. What was it?", "correct_answer": "A 33-rpm record", "incorrect_answers": ["A U.N. flag", "A hologram of the map of the world", "A U.S. silver dollar"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This actor, whose children are named Jane and Peter, was Juror # 8 in 12 Angry Men.", "correct_answer": "Henry Fonda", "incorrect_answers": ["Lee J. Cobb", "James Stewart", "Ed Begley Sr."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Each king in a deck of playing cards represents a great king from history.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What word denotes the government of a nation or state?", "correct_answer": "polity", "incorrect_answers": ["municipality", "civility", "policity"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What season is it when Bambis mother is shot by the poachers in the movie Bambi?", "correct_answer": "winter", "incorrect_answers": ["spring", "fall", "summer"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the popular song written by American composer Joseph Winner in 1869?", "correct_answer": "Little Brown Jug", "incorrect_answers": ["Little Brown Bug", "Little Brown Child", "Little Brown Chair"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This active volcano, whose name means long mountain in Hawaiian, is one of the five peaks that form the Island of Hawaii.", "correct_answer": "Mauna Loa", "incorrect_answers": ["Cotopaxi", "Mount Kea", "Hekla"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the common name of the national flower of India, which is also called Sacred water lily and is often associated with Buddhism?", "correct_answer": "Lotus", "incorrect_answers": ["Chamomile", "Dahlia", "Poppy"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Venus has the densest atmosphere in the solar system.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What fields did the science of alchemy originally combine?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Metallurgy and astrology", "Chemistry and medicine", "Art and physics"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This is the vitamin that vegetarians should take, as it is not found in plants.", "correct_answer": "B 12", "incorrect_answers": ["A", "C", "E"]}]